

# ₩ Date of birth 01/15/1994

A St 35, Glendown Avenue

O Dublin

+1 936 657 1605

### **Basic Skills**

Html, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Php, Python, Liquid

### **Frontend Skills**

Tailwincss, SCSS, PostCSS, SASS

React, Vue, NextJs, AlpineJS

#### **Fullstack Skills**

Nodejs, NestJS, Express, Ruby on Rails, GraphQL

### **Shopify Skill**

**Shopify Theme Customization** 

**Shopify Theme Build** 

**StoreFront** 

**Shopify API** 

### Languages

**English** 

### **Jason ALLEN**

## **Shopify Developer**

Passionate Shopify developer with extensive experience in theme customization, building, and store front development. Transforming Shopify stores into captivating digital experiences is my expertise. With a keen eye for detail and a commitment to delivering exceptional results, I excel in creating visually stunning and user-friendly websites. Let me leverage my skills to drive success for your business.

### **Education**

### **Bachelor Degree of Computer Science**

From September 2012 to September 2016 National College of Ireland Dublin, Ireland

### **Work experience**

### Frontend Developer

From June 2015 to December 2018

Digital Marketing Agency 42 Pearse St, Dublin, D02 YX88, Ireland

- -Worked with UX/UI design teams improve existing applications and increase conversion rates by 20%.
- -Designed multiple dynamic and browser compatible pages using HTML5, CSS3, Javascript (React, Redux).
- -Optimizing applications for maximum speed
- -Collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability

### Shopify Developer

From June 2019 to June 2023

Web Bureau 39-40 Mayor Street Upper, Dublin

- -Custom Shopify theme development from scratch.
- -Proven hands-on experience in efficiently developing Shopify custom storefront, a kind of headless commerce.
- -Conversion Rate Optimization
- -Google Analytics and Facebook Pixel
- -Page Speed Optimization